jzip.com 2011-12-28

# jZip | Free zip software download - Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

Bandoo Media Inc. ("jZip") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about jZip's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how jZip receives, collects and uses information in connection with their website located at jZip.com ("Site").

## Collection and Use of Information

#### Information You Provide:

When you register on the Site, you will be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information, which may include your name, email address, age, gender, address, telephone number(s), areas of interest, login name, login password and other self-identifying information (all "Personal Information"). jZip collects Personal Information primarily for the following purposes: (i) to maintain a record of registered users; (ii) to manage the login process and maintain users' personal preferences; (iii) to email registered users with news and updates; and (iv) to email promotional offers. In addition, jZip may also collect information about you in surveys or for sweepstakes and contests on the Site and information about the searches you perform, promotional offers you choose and the pages you visit on the Site.

jZip may also make certain message boards and forums available to you (collectively, "Forums"). You are solely responsible for the information and other content you post on and through these Forums and should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose Personal Information on or through these Forums, such information is generally accessible to and may be collected and used by other users. This Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. You are encouraged to exercise discretion when providing personal information about themselves in and through Forums.

#### Information We Automatically Collect:

jZip does not automatically collect any Personal Information on or through the Site, except as provided by you in connection with the registration process. Nevertheless, jZip may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at jZip's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. jZip's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

jZip may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. jZip collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. jZip will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

## Sharing and Disclosure of Information

jZip does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. jZip may disclose your Personal Information if jZip believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on jZip; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of jZip (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of jZip services or members of the public.

jZip may share aggregated demographic information about users with third party advertising and content companies. This information does not identify individual users and jZip do not link aggregate user data with Personal Information. 

## Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the jZip website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

## Security 

jZip takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although jZip cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, jZip has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

## Business Transitions

In the event that jZip goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. jZip will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information jZip may have prior to such transfer.

## Changes to Policy

From time to time, jZip may revise this Policy. jZip will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information jZip collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.

## Change or Removal of Information

You can edit your Personal Information at any time by logging in to your account and editing your profile.

When user registers on the Site, the user may have the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from jZip, including offers, updates and newsletters. If a user chooses not to opt-in, the user will not receive any communication from jZip. If a user's e-mail address changes, a user may correct such information by sending an e-mail to [support@jZip.com](mailto:support@jZip.com)  with the request or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. If a user no longer wishes to receive e-mail communication from jZip, a user may opt-out of receiving such communications by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. In addition, a user can remove their e-mail address at any time by sending an e-mail with the subject line of OPT-OUT to [support@jZip.com](mailto:support@jZip.com)

## Contact Information

Please direct all questions in connection with this Policy via e-mail to [privacy@jZip.com](mailto:privacy@jZip.com)  or by writing to Bandoo Media Inc., Attention: Privacy Policy Administrator, 40 Kimonos St.3095 Limassol, Cyprus. 

|    
[Join Our Affiliate Program](http://www.matomymarket.com/BrandedPublisherRegistration/jzip/) | About Us | Privacy Policy | Terms of Use | DMCA Policy

Copyright © 2011 All Rights Reserved to Bandoo Media Inc. | First jZip by Greg Kowal

jZip supports the following extentions: zip, jar, xpi, 7z, arj, bz2, bzip2, tbz2, tbz, cab, chm, chi, chq, chw, hxs, hxi, hxr, lit, msi, doc, xls, ppt, cpio, deb, gz, gzip, tgz, tpz, iso, lzh, lha, rar, rpm, tar, wim, swm, z, taz.   
® WinZip is a registered trademark of ® WinZip International LLC. jZip is not sponsored by or affiliated with ® WinZip in any manner
